ROMAN BOGOUDINOV

VETERAANINTIE 1 B 13 57230 SAVONLINNA +358 40 845 53 32 R.BOGOUDINOV@MAC.COM WWW.ROMAN-B.COM

BIRTH 03.11.1982 SAINT-PETERSBURG, RUSSIA



Seek for a job or (and) internship

- Web development
- IT technical staff (cable networks, helpdesk service)
- System administrator Microsoft Windows Server, AD, Linux, Azure, virtualization (MS, VMware)

My past working experience mostly in a different field, but it always been related to IT somehow. I always been interested in tech and coding, and after years of work in other fields, I decided to do what I always wanted, become a software developer, and moved to Finland to start my studies, pursuing new career path.

During the studies I developed two web applications and several smaller study projects, which helped me to gain skills in front-end and backend development. I have got solid knowledge and practical experience with JS, React, Node.js, HTML+CSS(SASS), SQL,MongoDB. I would like to join the development team as a Junior Web developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

7/1/2006 — 1/5/2007 PLANET LLC. Russia, Moscow region

SALES MANAGER (SALED DEPT "GOODS AND MATERIALS FOR WINDOWS MAKERS)

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Searching for the new clients on local market
- Organizing meetings with potential clients
- Carrying out a bargains
- Payments controlling
- Service and support branches of company in other regions of country

5/2/2007 - 2/15/2008 PLANET LLC. Russia, Moscow region

SENIOR MANAGER OF SALES DEPARTMENT

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Existing clients service
- Developing of client's network in regions of country
- Service and support branches of company in other regions of country
- Representing company at Local and International Exhibitions (MosBuild, FensterBau Frontale, Bautec)
- Employees training (Start trainings for Sales office, coaching)
- Extra experience: Developed and implemented whole new IT infrastructure in Company.

2/18/2008 — 01/23/2009 ALEMAR DEVELOPMENT OJSC Russia, Moscow

SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR OF DEPARTMENT OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

RESPONSIBILITIES

- IT service (Supporting part of Servers Forest, Network service, telephony, workstations and remote workstations)
- Communicating with other departments of business structure of company
- IT Helpdesk for users
- Administration Trade and Financial databases

GENERAL MANAGER

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Deploying a new branch of Moscow based company in Saint Petersburg
- Staff hiring
- Managing a work process of branch
- Developing client's network on local market
- Training sales staff and sales coaching
- Stock planning
- Supply logistic and delivery
- Sales dept improving, employee's attestation, making sales goals to growth the company
- Communicating with State tax services and successful passing state Taxes checkups
- Financial controlling and successful experience of suing with debtors
- Extra experience: Successfully moved a branch of company to a new place without breaks in service for clients

5/21/2015 - 10/31/2017Petersburg KOMPLEKTSERVIS LLC. (NORTH-WEST BRANCH) part of profine.RUS (profine GMBH)

Russia, Saint-

GENERAL MANAGER

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Staff hiring
- Managing a work process of branch
- Developing client's network on local market
- Stock planning
- Supply logistic and delivery
- Sales dept improving, employee's attestation, making sales goals to growth the company
- Communicating with State tax services and successful passing state Taxes checkups
- Financial controlling and successful experience of suing with debtors

5/21/2015 - 2/27/2020

GST LLC.

Russia, Saint-Petersburg

HEAD OF DEPT "CONSTRUCTING WINDOWS, DOORS, GLASSING"

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Managing constructing projects
- Developing projects of production windows and doors for Customers
- Production and works planning
- Supply logistic and delivery
- Communicating with customer to on construction works check ups according the project till final of constructing building
- Guarantee customer service
- Financial controlling

2/24/2021 — now

RTK-Henkilöstöpalvelu Oy

Suomi, Punkaharju

Maintenance team's member (part-time job)

RESPONSIBILITIES

Cleaning and maintaining heavy industrial machinery at METSÄ WOOD PLANT PUNKAHARJU – part-time job (shifts only on Sundays)

7/13/2021 - now

RB ICT PALVELUT (Entrepreneurship)

Suomi, Savonlinna

ENTREPRENEUR

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Solving problems with customer's hardware
- Developing brand new LAN/WAN and scale client's networks.
- Setting-up networks, workstations, and servers
- Web-design, creating and supporting websites

EDUCATION:

09/1997-05/2002 College of Saint-Petersburg State University of Aerospace instrumentation (Russia)

Grade: Technician (Junior Engineer)

- Specialization: Computing systems, complexes and Networks
- One year duration course "Business management"

09/2002-05/2004 Saint-Petersburg State University of Aerospace instrumentation

(Russia)

Faculty of Economics (not graduated)

Specialization: Business Management

03/2020-04/2021 SAMledu Ammattiopisto

(Finland, Savonlinna)

Vocational qualification in information and Communication Technology, 341101; Part 1

Hardware and software maintenance, 1pYLTO, 30 osp

Taloustieteen tiedekunta (ei valmistunut)

08/2020 - 09/2022 SAMIedu Ammattiopisto

(Finland,Savonlinna)

- Software development/IT-services
- Hardware and software maintenance 341102 /2019

Other education:

Additional courses:

Aalto Uni - Web development

LUT - Software development skills: Full-stack

LUT - Web applications, Front-end skills, Mobile applications.

LUT - Software and system architectures

Helsinki university - Full stack web development (JS,React)

TAU - Programming: Structures (C++, GUI projects, Qt)

LANGUAGES:

English

Russian

Finnish

About myself:

I'm Native Russian. Was born in Leningrad (now Saint Petersburg) Parts of my family lives in Far East of Russia and South of Russia. For now, I live in Savonlinna (Finland). Ready to move. In love with travels, nature and gadgets. I have high communication skills, friendly and respectful to other people. Would love to take a part of company where I can get new opportunities and bring my experience to grow together.

Ready to study and learn new.

Recommendations available on request.